Narrator: 1
Anya: This is me and my mum in York.
It was my first term at university, and she came to visit me,
and I took her on a tour round the city.
Friend: Is that, er, the cathedral there?
Anya: Yes – well, it’s called York Minster, but it’s really a cathedral.
Narrator: 2
Anya: And this one’s on the beach in Cornwall with my boyfriend, Ollie.
I was staying with him in the Easter holidays, and he took me to the beach and we went for a walk.
Friend: It looks windy!
Anya: Yes, it was really windy and cold.
I think we were the only people on the beach!
Narrator: 3
Friend: Nice photo! I like the moustache.
Anya: Yeah, that’s me and my friend Maisie.
We were doing a music course – I do it twice a year,
and this was at the party at the end of the course.
Friend: Why the moustaches and the picture frame?
Anya: There was this corner that the teachers made
where people could take funny photos with the big frame, and hats and moustaches and things.
Narrator: 4
Anya: OK, this one is me and two of my best friends –
we were at school together.
One of them, Libby, the one on my right, has a house by the river,
and we went there in September before we all went to university.
Narrator: 5
Friend: That’s a nice photo.
In Rome, I guess?
Anya: Yes, I was there for a holiday with my mum the summer before I went to university.
She took this when we were visiting the Colosseum – as you can see.
Narrator: 6
Friend: That’s your mum again, isn’t it?
Anya: Yes, that’s her and her partner, and my sister Roz, on the river in Oxford.
My mum’s birthday is in July, and every year we go punting and then we go for dinner.
We were all drinking champagne, and Roz was doing the hard work!
Friend: Are any of the photos selfies?
Anya: Yes, the one of me and my mum and the one on the beach.